reporting that I saw in liberal media was,
it seemed to suggest that I had deserved it
because they branded me far right.
And some even went so far as to suggest
that I maybe faked my injuries.
A Buzzfeed reporter asked for my medical records,
which I did provide, but this felt so,
it's like, because I didn't die in that attack,
there was another round of people
who wanted to finish me off.
But I continued, and then 2020,
Portland was really the epicenter
of the longest political violence.
Those months of riots, I was on the ground, undercover,
and there was an assassination there.
There was a supporter of Donald Trump named Aaron Danielson
who was shot dead by a self-described Antifa member
who then fled out of state
and died in a shootout with US Marshals.
In 2021, I returned undercover,
naively thinking that enough time had passed,
and was chased through the streets of downtown
and beaten, nearly choked out.
The person who was trying to choke me out
held me so tightly that I had the blood,
the vessels in my eyes burst.
So one of the symptoms where my eyes were completely bread
after that, and I was hospitalized.